Guide to the Ray Lyman Wilbur, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0064A
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- 1922-1923, Series 7
  - Recommendations (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Registrar (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Rhodes Scholarships (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Romanic Languages (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Russian (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - S, general (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - S, general (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Salaries (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - School of Biology (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Social Service Board (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Stanford Clinics Auxiliary (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Stanford Dramatic Council (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Home for Convalescent Children (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Stanford National Board (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Union (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Union, 1912-1917 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Union, 1917-1921 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Summer Quarter (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - T (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Trustees, Individual (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - U (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Unique (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - University Day (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - V (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - W (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Women's Conference and Council (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Y (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - YMCA and YWCA (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Z (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Zoology (Box 67, Folder 3)
- 1923-1924, Series 8
  - A (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Admission - Stanford children (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Secretary (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Anatomy (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Applied Mathematics (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Appointment Office (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Assistants, 1922-23 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Associated Students (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Ba (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Bacteriology (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Be - Bi (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Bi - Bo (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Blodgett, D. P. (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Botany (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Botulism (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Br - By (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Ca - Cl (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - California, Univ. Of (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Chemistry (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Citizenship (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Civil Engineering (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Classical Literature (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Co - Cy (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Commencement (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Comptroller, 1923 Sept. - 1924 Feb. (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Comptroller, 1924 Mar. - Aug. (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Dean of Women (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Education (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Electrical Engineering (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Engineering (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Fraternities (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - German (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Glee Club (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - History (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Hoover War Library (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Jordan, David Starr (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Law (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Library (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Medical School (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Medical School, Report of Work Done in Surgical Pathology Laboratory (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Mining and Metallurgy (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Museum (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Physical Education: Encina (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - Physical Education: Roble (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Physics (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Physiology (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Political Science (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Psychology (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Q (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Ra - Re (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Recommendation, Letters of (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Registrar (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Rhodes Scholarships (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Ro - Ry (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Romanic Languages (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Scholarship Committee (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - School of Social Sciences (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - School of Social Sciences (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Social Service Board (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - St - Sy (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Clinics Auxiliary (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Home for Convalescent Children (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Stanford National Board (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Union (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Student's Guild (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Student Publications (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Summer Quarter, 1924 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - U. S. Veteran's Bureau (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Trustees (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Ta - Ty (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Unique (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - U - V (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - West Memorial Lectures (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Wa - Wy (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - X, Y, Z (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - YMCA (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Zoology (Box 71, Folder 15)
- 1924-1925, Series 9
  - A (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - A (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Alumni and Academic Secretary (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Anatomy (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Applied Mathematics (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Appointment Office (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Assistants (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Assistants (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Associated Students (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Ba - By (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Bacteriology (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Bequests (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Biology, School of (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Biology, School of (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Blodgett, D. P. (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Athletics (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Agreement, Triangular (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Botany (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Ca - Cl (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - California, Univ. Of (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Chemistry (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Citizenship (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Civil Engineering (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Classical Literature (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Co - Cy (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Collins, Jr., J. (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Comptroller (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Comptroller (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - D (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Dean of Men (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Dean of Women (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - E (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Economics (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Education (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Electrical Engineering (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Military Science and Tactics (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Endowment (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - English (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Engineering Education (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Engineering Education (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - F (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Fellowships (Foreign) (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Fraternities (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Ga - Gy (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - General Election Board (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Geology (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - German (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Ha - Hy (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - History (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - I (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - J (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Jordan, David Starr (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Ka - Ky (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - La - Ly (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Lane Medical Lectures (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Law (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Library (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Mathematics (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Me - My (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Mechanical Engineering (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Medical School (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Medical School (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Medical School (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Memorial Church (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Men's Council (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Mining and Metallurgy (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Museum (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - N (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Natural History Museum (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - National Research Council (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Nursery (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - O (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - P (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Palo Alto Hospital (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Philosophy (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Physical Education: Encina (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Physical Education: Roble (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Physics (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Physiology (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Political Science (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Psychology (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Publicity (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Quad (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Ra - Ri (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Recommendations (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Registrar (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Rhodes Scholarships (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Romanic Languages (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - St - Sy (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Slavic (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Social Sciences, School of (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Social Service Board (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Sororities (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Alumni Award (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Clinics Auxiliary (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Convalescent Home (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Stanford National Board (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Stanford University Press (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Summer Quarter (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - T (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Trustees (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Unique (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - U. S. Dept. of State (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - U. S. Veteran's Bureau (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - U - V (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Wa - Wy (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - West Memorial Lecture (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Women's Council (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - X, Y, Z (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - YMCA (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Zoology (Box 80, Folder 22)
- 1925-1926, Series 10
  - A (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Association (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - American, various (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Anatomy (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Applications / Positions (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Applications / Positions (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Appointment Office (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Assistants (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Assistants (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Bacteriology (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Ba - By (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Be (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Bequests (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Classical Literature (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Dean of Women (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - E - misc. (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Biology, School of (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Co - misc. (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Daily Palo Alto (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Club (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Blodgett, D. P. (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Commencement (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Dormitories (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Fellowships [foreign] (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Commonwealth Fund (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Dramatic Council (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Comptroller, 1925 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - E - misc. (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Fraternities (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Botany (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Comptroller, January - March 1926 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Economics (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Ga - misc. (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Business, Graduate School of (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Comptroller, April - May 1926 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Education (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - General Education Board (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Ca - Cl (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Comptroller, June - October 1926 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Electrical Engineering (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Geology (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - California, Univ. Of (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - D - misc. (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Electrical Engineering - Ryan High Voltage Lab (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - German (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Dean of Men (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Endowment (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Illegal football (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Chemistry (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Engineering Education (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Military Science & Tactics (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Citizenship (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - English (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Civil Engineering (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - English - Public Speaking (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Clark, letters (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - J (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Jordan, David Starr (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Ka (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Ke (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - L (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Lane medical Lectures (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Law (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Letters, School of (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Li (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - M (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Mathematics (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Mechanical Engineering (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Medical School (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Medical School (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Medical School (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Medical School (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Medical School (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Medical School (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Medical School: Applications (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Memorial Church (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Men's Council (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Mi (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Mining and Metallurgy (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Ms (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Museum (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - N (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Nursing (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - O (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Pa (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Palo Alto Hospital (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Patients (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Philosophy (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - Physical Education: Encina (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - Physical Education: Roble (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Physical Sciences, School of (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Physics (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Physiology (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Political Science (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Psychology Department (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Publicity (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Pi - Q (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Quad (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Questionnaires (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - R (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Recommendations (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Religion, School of (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Religion, School of (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Rhodes Scholarships (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - R - Rn (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Ro (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Romanic Languages (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - S (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Social Sciences, School of (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Slavic (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Sm (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Social Service Board (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Sororities (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - St (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Band (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Convalescent Home (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Stanford National Board (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Press (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Su (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Summer Quarter (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - T (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Unique (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - W - We (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - W - We (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - W - We (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - West Memorial Lectures (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Wh (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - Wo (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - Women's Council (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - YMCA (Box 86, Folder 23)
  - Zoology (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - X, Y, Z (Box 87, Folder 2)
- 1926-1927, Series 11
  - A (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Secretary (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - American (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - American (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - American (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Assistants (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Assistants (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Assistants (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Anatomy (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Appointment Office (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Associated Students (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Ba (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Bacteriology (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Bequests to the Univ. (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Big Game Tickets, Requests for (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Biology (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Blodgett, D. P. (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Botany (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Br (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Bu (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Burbank Foundation (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Burbank Foundation (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Burbank Foundation (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Ca (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - California, University Of (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Ch (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Chemistry (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Citizenship (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Classical Literature (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Co (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Commonwealth Fund (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Comptroller (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Comptroller (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Da (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Dean of Men (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Dean of Women (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Dentistry (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Do (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Dramatic council (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - E (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Economics (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Education (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - Engineering, School of (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - Engineering, Electrical (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - Engineering, Military Service (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Endowments (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Engineering, Civil (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Engineering, Mechanical (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Engineering, Mining and Metallurgy (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - English (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - English, Public Speaking (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Fa (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Fees (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Fellowships, Foreign, etc. (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Fellowships, Foreign, etc. (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - F (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - American-German Student Exchange (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Fraternities (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Ga (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - General Education Board (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Geology (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - German (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - G (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Graduate School of Business (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Ha (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Herzstein Lectures (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - History (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Hoover War Library (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - I (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - J (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Jordan, Dr. David Starr (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Journalism (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Junior College (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Junior College (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Junior College (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - K (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - L (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Lane Medical Lectures (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Law (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Letters, School of (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Library (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - M (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Mathematics (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Memorial Church (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Men's Council (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Medical School (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Medical School (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Medical School (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Medical School (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Medical School (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Medical School (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Museum (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Music, School of (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - N (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - National (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Nursing (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Nursing Schools, Comm. On Grading of (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - O (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - P (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Palo Alto Hospital (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Personnel (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Philosophy (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Physical Education: Encina (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Physical Education: Encina (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Physical Education: Roble (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Physics (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - Physical Sciences (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - Physiology (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - Political Science (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - Psychology (Box 93, Folder 19)
  - R (Box 93, Folder 20)
  - Recommendations (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Regional Plan (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Registrar (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Registrar (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Rhodes Scholarship Committee (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - R (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Rockefellar Foundation (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Rockefellar Foundation (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Romanic Languages (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - S (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Slavic (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Social Sciences, School of (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Social Science Research Council (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Sororities (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Social Service Board (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Daily (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Stanford National Board (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Stanford University Press (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Student's guild (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Summer Quarter (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - T (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Trustees (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - U (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Unique (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - W (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - West Lecture Series (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Western Commercial School, Secretaries (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Women's Council (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - X, Y, Z (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - YMCA and YWCA (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Zoology (Box 95, Folder 10)
- 1927-1928, Series 12
  - A (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - American (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Alumni and Academic Secretary (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Anatomy (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Applications (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Applications (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Appointment Secretary (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Assistants (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Assistants (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Assistants (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Associated Students (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - B (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Bacteriology (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Bequests (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Berkeley Schools (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Biology (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Blodgett, D. P. (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Big Game Tickets (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Botany (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Branner Seismometer Station (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - C (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - California, University Of (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Carnegie Corporation (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Chemistry (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Chemistry (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Citizenship (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Classical Literature (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Commencement (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Commonwealth Fund (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Comptroller (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Comptroller (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Comptroller (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Comptroller (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - D (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Dean of Men (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Dean of Women (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Dormitories (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Dramatic Council (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - E (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Economics (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Education (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Education (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Endowment (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Endowment (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Engineering, School of (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Engineering, Civil (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Engineering, Electrical (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Engineering, Mechanical (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Fraternities (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Guggenheim Laboratory (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Military Science and Tactics (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Mining and Metallurgy (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - English (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - English: Public Speaking (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - F (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Fellowships, Foreign (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Sigma Chi (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Medical School (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - G (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - General Education Board (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - General Education Board (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Geology (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - German (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Graduate School of Business (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - H (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Herzstein, Estate of (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - History (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Hoover War Library (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - I (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Internal Revenue (Survey Race Relations) (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Japanese Immigration (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - J (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Jordan, David Starr (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Journalism (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Junior Colleges, Elimination of Lower Division (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - K (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - L (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Lane Medical Lectures (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Law (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Letters, School of (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Library (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - Mathematics (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - M (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Medical School (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Medical School (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Medical School (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Medical School (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Memorial Church (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Men's Council (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - National (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Nursing (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Museum (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Music, School of (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - N (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - O (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - P - Q (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - Palo Alto Hospital (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - Philosophy (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Physical Education (men) (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Physical Education (women) (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Physical Sciences, School of (Box 102, Folder 4)